Guide to the BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
- Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
  - Code no.7401-1: John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Code no.7402-1: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1954-1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    1954-1959, 1962-1966
  - Code no.7412: Seattle-First National Bank and FirstBank Independent Employees Association, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Series XV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
  - Code no.1685: E.R. Squibb and Sons, Institute for Medical Research and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-438, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Series XVI: Industry Code #55, Management of Companies and Enterprises
  - Code no.7911: Producer and Office Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 174, 1961-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Series XVII: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
  - Code no.390: Milk Dealers (Philadelphia and Vicinity) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local Unions 463, 676, and 331, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Code no.6334-1: Standard Oil Company, Amoco Oil Company and Central States Petroleum Union Affiliates, Local 108, 1969- 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Code no.7405-1: Building Managers Association of Chicago and Elevator Operators' and Starters' Union, Local 66, AFL-CIO, 1961- 1966 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Code no.7409-1: Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations and Building Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 32B, 1964- 1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Code no.7410-1: Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations and Building Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 32B, 1960- 1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Code no.7411-1: Bronx Realty Advisory Board and Building Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 32E, 1954- 1966 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Code no.7414-1: Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations and Building Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 32J, 1963- 1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Code no.7414-2: Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations and Building Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 32J, 1969- 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Code no.7901-1: Building Maintenance Employers Association and Window Cleaners' Union, Local 2, 1959-1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Code no.7902-1: Building Service League and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 32J, 1959-1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Code no.7903-1: Pittsburgh Buildings Association and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 29, AFL-CIO, 1958- 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Code no.7903-2: Pittsburgh Buildings Association and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 29, AFL-CIO, 1964- 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Code no.7933: Esso Research and Engineering Co., New Jersey and Independent Laboratory Employees, 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Code no.7942: Bay Area Security Agencies, San Francisco, CA and International Union of Guards and Watchmen, 1972-1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Series XVIII: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
  - Code no.7926-1: Affiliated Hospitals of San Francisco and California Nurses' Association, 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Code no.7926-2: Affiliated Hospitals of San Francisco and California Nurses' Association, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Code no.7927: Associated Hospitals of East Bay and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1959-1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Code no.7929-1: Kaiser Foundation Hospitals, The Permanente Medical Group, Kaiser Foundation Health Plan and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Code no.7929-2: Kaiser Foundation Hospitals, The Permanente Medical Group, Kaiser Foundation Health Plan and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1956-1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Code no.7929-3: Kaiser Foundation Hospitals, The Permanente Medical Group, Kaiser Foundation Health Plan and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Code no.7941: Chicago Nursing Home Association and Building Service Employees' International Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO, 1966- 1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Code no.7949: Seattle Area Hospital Council and Washington State Nurses Association, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Code no.7952: Youngstown Hospital Association and Building Service and Maintenance Union, Local 47. AFL-CIO, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Code no.7992: Greater Hartford Chapter of the American National Red Cross and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 1303, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Series XIX: Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
  - Code no.7924-1: League of New York Theaters; Industrial Shows and Actors' Equity Association, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Code no.7924-2: League of New York Theaters and Actors' Equity Association, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Code no.7925: Turf and Race Clubs: Hollywood, Los Angeles, Del Mar, Los Alamitos, Western Harness Racing Association and Building Service Employees International Union, Locals 193, 399, 102, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Series XX: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
  - Code no.7101: Arrowhead Food and Beverage Council and Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 84 and Bartenders Local 53, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Code no.7102: Restaurants of Oregon Association and Joint Executive Board of Culinary Crafts, Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 207, 305, 496, 664, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Code no.7105: East Bay Restaurant Association, Inc. and United Tavern Owners Association, Inc. and Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1959-1965 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Code no.7109: Harbor District Tavern and Restaurant Association and San Pedro Joint Executive Board of Hotel, Restaurant, Cafeteria, Motel Employees and Bartenders, Locals 512, 591, 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Code no.7103: Buckeye Retail Liquor and Beer Dealers' Association and Hamilton County Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Code no.7112: Long Beach and Orange County Restaurant Association and Bartenders and Culinary Workers Joint Executive Board of Long Beach and Orange County, 1948-1955 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Code no.7113: Metropolitan Restaurant Association, Detroit, Michigan and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Detroit Local Joint Executive Board, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Code no.7114-1: On-Sale Liquor Dealers of Minneapolis and Rural Hennepin County and Hotel an Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 152, 458, 665, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Code no.7114-2: On-Sale Liquor Dealers of Minneapolis and Rural Hennepin County and Hotel an Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 152, 458, 665, 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Code no.7115-1: Reno Employers Council and Reno Local Joint Executive Board of Bartenders, Culinary Workers, Locals 86 and 45, 1961- 1963 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Code no.7115-2: Reno Employers Council and Reno Local Joint Executive Board of Bartenders, Culinary Workers, Locals 86 and 45, 1963- 1969 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Code no.7116-1: Reno Employers Council, Lake Tahoe Resort Area and Reno Local Joint Executive Board of Bartenders, Culinary Workers, Locals 86 and 45, 1960-1965 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Code no.7116-2: Reno Employers Council, Lake Tahoe Resort Area and Reno Local Joint Executive Board of Bartenders, Culinary Workers, Locals 86 and 45, 1965-1971 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Code no.7117-1: Restaurant Hotel Employers' Council of Southern California and Los Angeles Local Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees Unions, 1950-1959 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Code no.7117-2: Restaurant Hotel Employers' Council of Southern California and Los Angeles Local Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees Unions, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Code no.7118: San Joaquin Valley Hotel, Restaurant and Tavern Association and Local Joint Executive Board of Cooks, Pastry Cooks and Assistants Union, Locals 230 and 62, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Code no.7119-1: Santa Barbara Restaurant Association and Ventura County Restaurant Owners Association and Culinary Alliance and Bartenders Local 498, 1960-1971 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Code no.7122-1: Washington State Restaurant Association and Seattle Hotel Association and Seattle Local Joint Executive Board, Locals 33, 239, 240, 487, 551, 1959-1966 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Code no.7123-1: Washington State Restaurant Association and Seattle Hotel Association and Hotel, Motel, and Restaurant Employees' Union Local 61 and Bartenders' Union Local 711, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Code no.7125-1: Restaurants in the Chicago, Illinois Area and Chicago Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 42, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Code no.7127: St. Louis Restaurant, Tavern and Cocktail Lounge Association; and Hotel and Motel Association of Greater St. Louis and St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, L, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Code no.7131: Restaurants and Cafeterias located in New York, New York and Cafeteria Employees Union, Local 302, affiliated with Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International, AFL- CIO, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Code no.7132: Detroit Restaurants Guild, Inc. and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Detroit Local Joint Executive Board, Locals 234, 562, 705, 880, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Code no.7133: Schrafft's Food Service division, Pet Inc. and Chain Restaurant and Luncheonette Union, Local 11, of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL- CIO, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Code no.7134: Bickford's, Inc. and Chain Service Restaurant Luncheonette and Soda Fountain Employees Union, Local 11, of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL- CIO, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Code no.7135: Restaurant League of New York, Inc. and Dining Room Employees Union, Local 1, of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Alf-CIO, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Code no.7138: Stouffer Foods Corporation and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Detroit Local Joint Executive Board, Locals 234, 562, 705, 880, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Code no.7144: Restaurant League of New York, Inc. and Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks, and Assistants Union, Local 89, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Code no.7148: Sacramento and Vicinity Hotel, Restaurant and Tavern Owners and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 49, AFL-CIO, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Code no.7501-1: Associated Hotels, Inc. and Hotel and Allied Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 144, 1959-1967 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Code no.7501-2: Associated Hotels and Motels, Inc. and Hotel and Allied Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 144, 1969- 1974 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Code no.7502-1: Chicago Residential Hotel Association and Hotel, Motel, and Apartment Hotel Employees' Union, Local 4 of the Building Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Code no.7504-2: Greater Boston Hotel and Motor Inn Association and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Locals 186, 34, 277, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Code no.7504-1: Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Locals 186, 34, 277 and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Locals 186, 34, 277, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Code no.7507: Chicago Residential Hotel Association and Local Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 25, 88, 278, 450, 484, 593, 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Code no.7508-1: Hotel Association of St. Louis and St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 51, 430, 26, 249, 20, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Code no.7508-2: Hotel and Motel Association of Greater St. Louis and St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 51, 430, 26, 249, 20, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Code no.7509-1: Hotel Association of New York City, Inc. and New York Hotel Trades Council, AFL-CIO, 1959-1967 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Code no.7509-2: Hotel Association of New York City, Inc. and New York Hotel Trades Council, AFL-CIO, 1966-1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Code no.7510-1: Hotel Association of Washington, D.C. and Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1957-1966 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Code no.7510-2: Hotel Association of Washington, D.C. and Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1966-1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Code no.7513: Chicago Downtown Hotels and Local Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 25, 88, 278, 450, 484, 593, 1959-1970 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Code no.7514: Minneapolis Area Hotels and Motels and Minneapolis Local Joint Executive Board of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 152, 458, 665, 1956-1968 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Code no.7516-1: Philadelphia Hotel Association and Philadelphia Hotel and Club Employees Union, Local 568 of Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1955-1960 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Code no.7518-1: Southern Florida Hotel and Motel Association and Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 255, 1959-1969 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Code no.7519-1: Detroit Hotel Association and Detroit Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders' International Unions, AFL-CIO, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Code no.7519-2: Detroit Hotel Association and Detroit Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees' and Bartenders' International Unions, AFL-CIO, 1962-1968 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Code no.7120 / 591071: St. Paul On-Sale Liquor Dealers and St. Paul Joint Executive Board, Bartenders Local 287, Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 556, 1963-1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Series XXI: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
  - Code no.6901: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and Northern Santa Clara County and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1965-1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Code no.7703-1: Chicago Dry Cleaners Association and Laundry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union, Local 46, 1961- 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Code no.7704: Chicago Laundry Owners Association and Laundry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union, Local 46, 1957- 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Code no.7705: Professional Laundry Institute of Chicagoland and Laundry, Dye House, Cleaning Drivers, Chauffeurs, Handlers, Solicitors, and Salesmen, Local 712, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Code no.7707: Dry Cleaning and Laundry Institute of Detroit, Inc. and Detroit and Midwestern States Joint Board of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Code no.7708: Empire State Chain Store Cleaners Association and Cleaners, Dyers, Pressers, Drivers and Allied Trades Union, Local 239, AFL-CIO, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Code no.7712: Los Angeles Laundry Owners Association and Laundry and Dry Cleaning Workers International Union, Local 52, 1961- 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Code no.7714-1: New Jersey Laundry and Cleaning Institute and Laundry Workers, Cleaners and Dyers Union, Local 284, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Code no.7714-2: New Jersey Laundry and Cleaning Institute and Hospital Services, Laundry, Cleaners and Miscellaneous Workers, Local 284, AFL-CIO, 1970-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Code no.7719-1: Cleaners and Dyers Board of Trade, Inc. and Cleaners, Dyers, Pressers, Drivers, and Allied Trades Union, Local 239, AFL-CIO, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Code no.7720: Associated Linen Suppliers Laundry, Inc. and Laundry Workers, Cleaners and Dyers Union, Local 284, 1961-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Code no.7721: Associated Laundries, Inc. Portland, Oregon and Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers' International Union, Local 107, 1966-1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Code no.7722: New Jersey Laundry and Cleaning Institute and Laundry Workers, Cleaners and Dyers Union, Local 284, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Code no.7726: Los Angeles Barbershops and Journeymen Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists, and Proprietors' International Union of America, Local 1000, 1965-1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Code no.7943-1: National and International Trade Unions and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 2, 1962- 1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Code no.7943-2: National and International Trade Unions and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 2, 1968- 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)